Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 71, folder: 26 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Item 15: What is a Biologist?, Publication (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Item 16: We, The Upjohn Company, Publication (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Item 17: We, The Upjohn Company, Publication (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Item 18: Professional Careers in Accounting and Finance: Stepping Stones to Management, Publication (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Item 19: People at Work, Publication (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Item 20: Kalamazoo, Michigan, Publication (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Item 21: What is a Pharmacist?, Publication (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Item 22: We, The Upjohn Company, Publication (Box 71, Folder 26)
- Box: 71, folder: 27 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: The Growing World of Upjohn, Publication (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: What is a Career?, Publication (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - Item 3: The Story of an American Enterprise, Publication (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - Item 4: Business Conditions in Kalamazoo, Publication (Box 71, Folder 27)
    By Sherrill Cleland. October-November 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: What the Individual Firm Can do to Contribute to Business Stabilization, Publication (Box 71, Folder 27)
    By Harold C. Taylor. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Progress Through Science, Publication (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - Item 7: Upjohn Pamphlet, Publication (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - Item 8: The W. E. Upjohn Institute for Employment Research, Publication (Box 71, Folder 27)
    September 15, 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Job Opportunity Request, Publication (Box 71, Folder 27)
- Box: 71, folder: 28 (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Upjohn Annual Report 1969, Publication (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Item 2: Upjohn Annual Report 1968, Publication (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Item 3: Upjohn Annual Report 1967, Publication (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Item 4: Homemakers, Inc. Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Item 5: Company Information Sheet for the Upjohn Company: Fine Pharmaceuticals Since 1886, Publication (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Item 6: Upjohn Offers Opportunities in Accounting and Finance, Publication (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Item 7: "CQ" Comment and Question Program, Publication (Box 71, Folder 28)
    January 25, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Item 9: Upjohn Annual Report 1966, Publication (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Item 10: Upjohn News, Publication (Box 71, Folder 28)
    June 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Upjohn News, Publication (Box 71, Folder 28)
    March 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Kalamazoo Arts Council, Inc., Publication (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Item 13: Upjohn Research, Publication (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Item 14: Homemakers is help., Publication (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Item 15: Upjohn News, Publication (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Item 16: Upjohn Annual Report 1960, Publication (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Item 17: Upjohn Annual Report 1964, Publication (Box 71, Folder 28)
- Box: 71, folder: 29 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Full Employment Through Business Enterprise: Five Years of Research in One Community, Publication (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Item 2: Shortages of Skilled Manpower, Publication (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Item 3: The W. E. Upjohn Institute's New Headquarters Building, Publication (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Item 4: Employee Attitudes and Productivity, Publication (Box 71, Folder 29)
    By Charles C. Gibbons. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: A Review of the First Decade and a Preview of the Second, Publication (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Item 6: Managing for Tomorrow, Publication (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Item 7: Employment of the Older Worker, Publication (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Item 8: Management Controls: An Annotated Bibliography, Publication (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Item 9: Prerequisites for a Guaranteed Annual Wage, Publication (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Item 10: The Guaranteed Annual Wage and Business Stabilization: A Bibliography, Publication (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Item 11: Stabilization of Employment is Good Management, Publication (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Item 12: Research, Bussiness, and Employment, Publication (Box 71, Folder 29)
    By Julius T. Wendzel. January 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Public Works Policies for Boom or Bust, Publication (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Item 14: A List of Books & Articles Prepared by the W. E. Upjohn Institute for Community Research, Publication (Box 71, Folder 29)
- Box: 72, folder: 1 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    July-August 1971. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    September 1971. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    June 1971. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    April 1971. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    March 1971. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    January 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    January-February 1971. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    September 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    December 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    July-August 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    June 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    March 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    April 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    January 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    October 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    September 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    July-August 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    June 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 24: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    April 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    March 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 27: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 28: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    October 1971. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    December 1971. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    January-February 1972. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    March 1972. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 33: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 34: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 35: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    September 1972. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    July-August 1972. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    June 1972. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 39: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 40: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    October 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 42: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 43: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 44: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 45: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 46: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 47: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 48: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 49: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 50: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 51: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 52: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    January-February 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 53: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 54: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 55: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 56: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    March 1973. Item is in English.
  - Item 57: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 58: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 59: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    September 1973. Item is in English.
  - Item 60: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    October 1973. Item is in English.
  - Item 61: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    December 1973. Item is in English.
  - Item 62: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    June 1973. Item is in English.
  - Item 63: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 64: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    January-February 1973. Item is in English.
  - Item 65: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 66: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    April 1973. Item is in English.
  - Item 67: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    July-August 1973. Item is in English.
  - Item 68: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    March 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 69: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    June 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 70: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    July-August 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 71: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 72: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 73: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    July-August 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 74: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    April 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 75: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 76: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    September 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 77: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    March 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 78: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 79: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 80: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    December 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 81: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    January-February 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 82: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    September 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 83: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    October 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 84: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 85: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 86: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 87: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    June 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 88: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    January-February 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 89: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 90: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    March 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 91: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    April 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 92: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 93: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    June 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 94: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    July-August 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 95: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    October 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 96: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    September 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 97: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    October 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 98: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    December 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 99: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Item 100: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 1)
    April 1972. Item is in English.
- Box: 72, folder: 2 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Group Benefits, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    March 1977. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    January-February 1977. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    April 1977. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    May 1977. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    June 1977. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    July-August 1977. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    September 1977. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    October 1977. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    November 1977. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    May 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    December 1977. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    January-February 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    March 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    April 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    May 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    June 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    July-August 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    September 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    October 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    November 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Item 24: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    December 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    January-February 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    March 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    April 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    June 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    July-August 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Upjohn Intercom, Publication (Box 72, Folder 2)
    September 1979. Item is in English.
- Box: 72, folder: 3 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Agreemet between Utah-Idaho Sugar Company and Beet Sugar Refinery Employee Locals, Publication (Box 72, Folder 3)
    August 1, 1959. Item is in English.
- Box: 72, folder: 4 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The W. E. Upjohn Institute for Community Research: A Review of the First Decade and a Preview of the Second, Publication (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: A Twenty-Year Review, Publication (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: A Twenty-Year Review, Publication (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Available Publications, Publication (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Available Publications, Publication (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: The Upjohn Institute: Personnel Programs Publications, Publication (Box 72, Folder 4)
    December 1961. Item is in English.
- Box: 72, folder: 5 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Bureau of Economic and Business Research, Publication (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: The Richest Hole on Earth: The History of the Bingham Copper Mine, Publication (Box 72, Folder 5)
- Box: 72, folder: 6 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: University of Utah Faculty Manual, Publication (Box 72, Folder 6)
- Box: 72, folder: 7 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: 1960 Annual Report, Publication (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Circuit, Publication (Box 72, Folder 7)
    March-April 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Circuit, Publication (Box 72, Folder 7)
    April 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: 1961 Annual Report, Publication (Box 72, Folder 7)
- Box: 72, folder: 8 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Publications of: The Utah Department of Employment Security, Publication (Box 72, Folder 8)
- Box: 72, folder: 9 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Going Through the Plant, Publication (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Of Making Many Books There is No End, Publication (Box 72, Folder 9)
- Box: 72, folder: 10 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: What Holds SAMI Back? A Study of Service Delivery in a Puerto Rican Community, Publication (Box 72, Folder 10)
- Box: 72, folder: 11 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Your Future with the Valley National Bank, Publication (Box 72, Folder 11)
- Box: 72, folder: 12 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: News Clippings, Publication (Box 72, Folder 12)
- Box: 72, folder: 13 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The Verbatim Survey, Publication (Box 72, Folder 13)
- Box: 72, folder: 14 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Annual Report 1966, Publication (Box 72, Folder 14)
- Box: 72, folder: 15 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Letter to Employers, Publication (Box 72, Folder 15)
- Box: 72, folder: 16 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: This is Vitro, Publication (Box 72, Folder 16)
- Box: 72, folder: 17 (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Careers: Research, Development, Engineering, Publication (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Employee Relations Policies for Salaried Personnel, Publication (Box 72, Folder 17)
    May 24, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Employment Application, Publication (Box 72, Folder 17)
- Box: 72, folder: 18 (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: 1974 Annual Report, Publication (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: 1970 Annual Report, Publication (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: 1969 Annual Report, Publication (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: 1968 Annual Report, Publication (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: 1967 Annual Report, Publication (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: 1966 Annual Report, Publication (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: Background Analysis and Special Report: Virginia Electric's Employee Information Program, Publication (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Item 8: 1971 Annual Report, Publication (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Item 9: 1972 Annual Report, Publication (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Item 10: 1973 Annual Report, Publication (Box 72, Folder 18)
- Box: 72, folder: 19 (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: "DAP" and "PET" Reproductions for Publication, Publication (Box 72, Folder 19)
- Box: 72, folder: 20 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Agreement between Narrow Fabric Workers Union and Vogt Mfg. Corporation, Publication (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Constitution and By-Laws, Publication (Box 72, Folder 20)
- Box: 72, folder: 21 (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Annual Report 1970, Publication (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: Annual Report 1966, Publication (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: Annual Report 1968, Publication (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: Annual Report 1969, Publication (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Item 5: Vulcan Materials Company Financial Report, Publication (Box 72, Folder 21)
    June 30, 1972. Item is in English.
- Box: 72, folder: 22 (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: The Fight for Free Enterprise, Publication (Box 72, Folder 22)
- Box: 72, folder: 23 (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Wallace News, Publication (Box 72, Folder 23)
    July-August 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Wallace News, Publication (Box 72, Folder 23)
    November-December 1952. Item is in English.
- Box: 73, folder: 1 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Your Company and Your Job, Publication (Box 73, Folder 1)
- Box: 73, folder: 2 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Timeline, Publication (Box 73, Folder 2)
- Box: 73, folder: 3 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Annual Report 1969, Publication (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: 1967 Annual Report, Publication (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Annual Report 1968, Publication (Box 73, Folder 3)
- Box: 73, folder: 4 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Employee Manual, Publication (Box 73, Folder 4)
- Box: 73, folder: 5 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Annual Report, Publication (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: 1961 Annual Report, Publication (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: 1960 Annual Report, Publication (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: 1960 Annual Report, Publication (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: 1960 Annual Report, Publication (Box 73, Folder 5)
- Box: 73, folder: 6 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Statement of Policy on Appointments Promotions and Tenure, Publication (Box 73, Folder 6)
- Box: 73, folder: 7 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Personnel Rules for the Classified, Publication (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: With WSU, Publication (Box 73, Folder 7)
- Box: 73, folder: 8 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: 1968-1969 Annual Report, Publication (Box 73, Folder 8)
    By Waterfront Commission of NY Harbor. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Pier Hirings Dip in February, Publication (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: January Dock Jobs in Port Show Sag; Unfilled Job Calls on Upswing, Publication (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: January Dock Jobs Up in Port of New York, Publication (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Contract Holidays and Blizzard Reduce Pier Jobs in Port of New York, Publication (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: March Job Calls In New York Port Move Up 25 Percent Over February; Unfilled Pier Jobs Continue Reports Dock Agency, Publication (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Waterfront Commission of NY Harbor, Publication (Box 73, Folder 8)
    By Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor Comparison of 1966 and 1965 Daily Hirings By Areas in the Port of New York. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Pier Agency Reports 1966 Dock Jobs in Port of New York Increased by 7%, Publication (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Seasonal Shipping Drop Reduces Port of New York June Dock Calls, Publication (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: Pier Hirings Dip in February, Publication (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: October Dock Jobs in the Port of New York SAG Slightly Despite 16-Day Strike, Publication (Box 73, Folder 8)
    By Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor. November 16, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Pier Job Calls in Port of New York During September Off by 15 Percent, Publication (Box 73, Folder 8)
    By Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor. October 30, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Dock Calls in New York Harbor Sagged During December; Job Calls Unfilled Exceed 9,600 Level, Publication (Box 73, Folder 8)
    By Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: News Release, Publication (Box 73, Folder 8)
    By Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor. July 14, 1971. Item is in English.